{
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "question": "Which of these characters wasn&#039;t a villian in Club Penguin?",
            "correct_answer": "The Director",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Herbert P. Bear",
                "Tusk",
                "Ultimate Proto-Bot 10000"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "question": "In the Lego Island trilogy, who taught Pepper Roni how to read?",
            "correct_answer": "Officer Laura Brick",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Papa Brickolini",
                "Officer Nick Brick",
                "Mama Brickolini"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "question": "What is the default name of the Vampire character in &quot;Shining Soul 2&quot;.",
            "correct_answer": "Bloodstar",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Sachs",
                "Dracuul",
                "Alucard"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "question": "In the Mario Kart series, which game introduced the &quot;Shield Drifting&quot; mechanic?",
            "correct_answer": "Mario Kart Arcade GP DX",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Mario Kart: Double Dash",
                "Mario Kart Super Circuit",
                "Mario Kart DS"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "question": "The voice actor for which Portal 2 character was not a TV or film actor prior to the game?",
            "correct_answer": "GLaDOS",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Cave Johnson",
                "Wheatley",
                "Atlas / P-Body"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "question": "The Bracken from Lethal Company is also known as:",
            "correct_answer": "The Flower Man",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "The Phantom",
                "The Shadow Demon",
                "Larry"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "question": "The &#039;D&#039; in the term &quot;D-Mail&quot; from the game &quot;Steins; Gate&quot; is short for what?",
            "correct_answer": "DeLorean",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Deep",
                "Demo",
                "Dev"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "question": "In the &quot;Little Lost Girl&quot; Easter Egg in Call of Duty: Black Ops II, what&#039;s the last step required for the achievement?",
            "correct_answer": "Raise Hell",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Freedom",
                "Skewer the Winged Beast",
                "Ascend from Darkness"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "question": "In the original &quot;Super Mario Bros.&quot;, what is the acceleration of Mario if he was in free fall?",
            "correct_answer": "91.28 m/s^2",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "110  m/s^2",
                "9.42  m/s^2",
                "4.4  m/s^2"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "question": "In &quot;Magicka&quot;, which two elements are combined to cast the spell, &quot;Nullify&quot;?",
            "correct_answer": "Arcane + Shield",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Lightning + Shield",
                "Lightning + Life",
                "Arcane + Life"
            ]
        }
    ]
}